Guide to the Vassar College Buildings and Grounds Files, 1879-2007 (bulk 1910-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- [Biological Sciences Building Specifications – Furnishing, Electrical and Mechanical], (3 folders) (Box 27)
- Utilities Gas Water Steam, 1969-1973 (Box 27)
- Invitations To Bid, 1971 (Box 27)
- Contract Award, 1971 (Box 27)
- Change Orders, 1978 (Box 27)
- [Biological Sciences Building – Finishing Work], 1972-1975 (Box 27)
- Biological Sciences Building Utilities – Gas, Water, Steam Engineers – Burns and Roe, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 27)
- Kendrick Alterations, 1975 (Box 27)
- Kendrick Alterations M. Idema, General Contractor, 1975 (Box 27)
- Kendrick Alterations Frank H. McEnaney, Inc., 1975 (Box 27)
- Town House Apartments Reports On Expenditure, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 27)
- Student Town House Apartments Architect Moore and Hutchins, 1971 (Box 27)
- Kendrick Alterations Shaker, Travis and Quinn, Inc., 1975 (Box 27)
- Student Town House Apartments Landscape Architect James S. Kennedy, 1971 (Box 27)
- Student Town House Apartments Contractor Eberhard Builders, Inc., 1971 (Box 27)
- Student Town House Apartments 330 Hooker Ave. Engineers, 1972 (Box 28)
- Town House Laundry Building Contractor – Eberhard Builders, Inc., 1973 (Box 28)
- Student Town House Apts. 330 Hooker Avenue General, 1971-1975 (Box 28)
- Student Apartments (Including Modular Housing Material), 1970-1971 (Box 28)
- Town House Apartments Furnishings, 1971 (Box 28)
- [Modular Housing Systems Inc.], 1970-1971 (Box 28)
- Town House Laundry Building, 1972-1973 (Box 28)
- Town House Laundry Building Shop Drawings, 1973; (3 folders) (Box 28)
- Town House Photos (Box 28)
- Student Apartments – Type “C” Specifications, 1971 (Box 28)
- Student Apartments – Type “C” Bids, 1971 (Box 28)
- Construction Daily Reports, 1971 (Box 28)
- Terrace Houses [Reports, Construction, Change Orders, Shop Drawings, Furnishings, Photos], 1972-1974; (9 folders) (Box 28)
- Dormitory Conversion [General Correspondence, Costs, Bills from Contractors and Work Reports], 1973-1974; (5 folders) (Box 28)
- Dormitory Conversion Phase II [Contractors, Specifications, General Correspondence], 1974-1975; (7 folders) (Box 28)
- Student Room Alterations, 1973 (Box 29)
- Proposed Renovation Of Dormitories General, 1968-1972 (Box 29)
- Renovation Of Dormitories Reports On Expenditure, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
- Renovation of Dormitories – Architects Goldstone, Dearborn and Hinz, 1972 (Box 29)
- Renovation of Dormitories Cost Consultants Wood and Tower, Inc., 1972 (Box 29)
- General, 1972 (Box 29)
- Student Housing Architects James Polshek, 1973 (Box 29)
- Student Housing Reports On Expenditures, 1973 (Box 29)
- New Dormitory Architect, 1965-1967 (Box 29)
- New Dormitory General, 1966 (Box 29)
- College Center, 1975-1979 (Box 29)
- College Center Reports On Expenditure, 1972-1979 (Box 29)
- [Payments To Dimeo Construction Company For College Center], 1975-1976 (Box 29)
- College Center Contractor Dimeo Construction Co., 1973-1975 (Box 29)
- College Center Fairway Testing Co., 1973-1974 (Box 29)
- College Center Cost Consultants Wood and Tower, Inc., 1972; (4 folders) (Box 29)
- College Center Architect Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson and Abbott, 1970-1976 (Box 29)
- College Center General, 1972-1975 (Box 29)
- College Center General, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
- College Center. Entrance-Anti-Skid, 1975 (Box 29)
- College Center Borings, 1972 (Box 30)
- College Center Furnishings, 1972-1974 (Box 30)
- College Center Guarantees, 1975-1976; (5 folders) (Box 30)
- College Center Hardware, 1973; (3 folders) (Box 30)
- College Center – Housing and Urban Development, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
- College Center Job Meeting Minutes, 1973-1975 (Box 30)
- [College Center Artist’s Rendering] (Box 30)
- College Center Photos, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
- College Center Paintings, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
- [Prison – Fixtures College Center], 1976 (Box 30)
- [Section 1140 Feed Service Equip. Vassar College Center], 1974; (2 folders) (Box 30)
- College Center Sound Module Details, 1974 (Box 30)
- College Center Sound System, 1975-1976; (2 folders) (Box 30)
- College Center Subcontractors, 1973 (Box 30)
- College Center Subcontractors Binghamton Steel, 1973-1975 (Box 30)
- College Center Transformers, 1973 (Box 30)
- College Center Change Orders, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
- College Center Change Proposals, 1973-1976 (Box 30)
- College Center Bids, 1973 (Box 30)
- Contract Award, 1970 (Box 30)
- Specifications (Box 30)
- Distribution Of Plans and Specs, 1973 (Box 30)
- Pool, 1973; (3 folders) (Box 30)
- Library Addition Contract Documents, 1974 (Box 30)
- Library Expansion Reports On Expenditures, 1973-1979 (Box 30)
- Library Addition – Contractor Warwick Construction, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 30)
- Library Addition – K and J/ Hok Interiors, 1975-1977 (Box 30)
- Library Expansion – Architect Hellmuth, Obata and Kassabaum, 1973-1978 (Box 30)
- Library Expansion Wood and Tower, Inc. – Cost Consultants, 1972 (Box 31)
- Library Addition – Library Consultant David Kaser, 1974 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Guarantees and Warranties, 1976-1977 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Job Meeting Minutes, 1974-1977 (Box 31)
- Library Addition, 1975-1978 (Box 31)
- Library Expansion, 1974 (Box 31)
- Library Expansion – General, 1972-1974 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Automatic Sprinkler Corp. Of America, 1974-1976 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Borings, 1974 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Furnishings, 1975-1976; (5 folders) (Box 31)
- Library Addition Hardware Schedule, 1975 (Box 31)
- Library Addition – Halon System, 1976-1977 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Vassar College Photos, 1975-1977 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Subcontractors, 1976 (Box 31)
- Distribution Of Plans and Specifications, Library Addition, 1974 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Change Orders, 1974-1984 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Specifications, 1974 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Pool, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 31)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Automatic Sprinkler Corp., 1975 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Misc. Shop Drawings, 1975 (Box 31)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Sullivan County Glass Co., 1975 (Box 31)
- [Kahn and Jacobs Architects, Vassar Library], 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings W. H. Kassner Inc., 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Additions Shop Drawings North American Door, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Otis Elevator, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings New Windsor Metal Fabricators, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawing Acme Steel Door Corporation, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Campbell Foundry, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings J and G Drywall, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Simplex, 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Thomas Stecklow Sons (Limestone), 1975 (Box 32)
- Dir. #4 Masonry, 1975 (Box 32)
- [Vassar Library Addition Drawing No. 5, Thomas Stecklow Sons], 1975 (Box 32)
- Library Addition Shop Drawings Bonhag Company, 1975-1976 (Box 32)
- [Vassar Library Addition Architectural Drawings], 1975 (Box 32)
- [Section 1140 Food Service Equip. Vassar College Center Crabtree Copy], 1974-1975 (Box 32)
- [College Center Shop Drawings Fisher Skylights Inc.], 1973 (Box 32)
- [College Center – Plumbing and Sprinkler Manuals], 1973-1975 (Box 33)
- [College Center Electricals], 1973-1974 (Box 33)
- [College Center H. V. A. C. Manuals], 1975 (Box 33)
- All College Dining Hall, 1972-1975 (Box 33)
- Dining Facility Students’ Building Rheinstein Construction Co., Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 33)
- Dining Facility Students’ Building Architect Walker O. Cain and Associates, 1970-1974 (Box 33)
- Dining Facility Students’ Building Cost Consultants Wood and Tower, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 33)
- Central Dining Facility Shop Drawings, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box 33)
- Dining Facility Students’ Building Engineers Burns and Roe, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 33)
- Central Dining Facility General, 1971-1983 (Box 33)
- Dining Facilities Proposed Renovation Of Students’ Building, 1969-1971 (Box 33)
- Central Dining Facility Change Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 33)
- Central Dining Facility Hardware, 1973 (Box 33)
- Central Dining Facility Furnishings, 1972-1973 (Box 34)
- Central Dining Facility Food Service Equipment, 1972-1973; (8 folders) (Box 34)
- Central Dining Facility – Transformers, 1971 (Box 34)
- Central Dining Facility Job Memos, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- [Job Meetings – Reports ], 1971-1973 (Box 34)
- [Maintenance Instructions – Electric Water Cooler Manual], 1970 (Box 34)
- [Vassar College Dining Hall Utilities], 1972 (Box 34)
- Distribution Of Plans and Specifications Central Dining Facility, 1971 (Box 34)
- Dining Facility (Students’ Building) Specifications, 1941 (Box 34)
- Dining Facility (Students’ Building) Invitations To Bid, 1971 (Box 34)
- Central Dining Facility Contract Award, 1971 (Box 34)
- H. V. A. C. Boilers, 1959-1985; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- Boiler Plant Cert, 1989 (Box 34)
- Boiler Feedwater Test Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 34)
- [Specifications and Contract Documents For Repair Of Boilers], 1980 (Box 34)
- [Application For Energy Conservation Measures (Projects) U. S. Department Of Energy Grant Program – For Boiler House, Vassar College], 1980 (Box 34)
- [Vassar College Boiler No. 5 – Operating Instructions For Bailey Meter Company, Boiler Combustion Control System], 1979 (Box 34)
- [Bailey Meter Proposal Revision To Vassar College Boiler House Controls], 1978 (Box 34)
- [Vassar College Boiler No. 5 – Operating Instructions], 1981 (Box 34)
- [Boiler Reports, Bailey Meter Company], 1978 (Box 34)
- Boiler House Summer Boiler, 1980 (Box 34)
- Boiler Alterations, 1976-1980 (Box 34)
- [Vassar College Buildings Report], 1942 (Box 34)
- Buildings Areas Sizes Etc., 1967-1979 (Box 34)
- Chalk and Bulletin Boards, 1987-1988 (Box 34)
- College Center, 1972-1980 (Box 34)
- C. H. P., 1989; (2 folders) (Box 34)
- [Alan Gaynor and Company Architectural and Interior Design], 1989 (Box 34)
- Commencement Signage, 1980-1985 (Box 34)
- [Contractors], 1988-1989 (Box 34)
- Dorms Lofts (Box 34)
- [Drawing-Drafting-Matl and Prices] (Box 34)
- [Electric – 4160 V Specs and Shop Drawings], 1957-1958 (Box 34)
- [Electric – 4160 V – Sub Station], 1955-1956 (Box 35)
- Underground Electrical Distribution System – February 3 ’85 Fault, 1985 (Box 35)
- Electrical Shutdown, 1985 (Box 35)
- Estimates, 1989-1990 (Box 35)
- Farm, 1963-1987 (Box 35)
- Fiber Optic/Audio Visual, 1974 (Box 35)
- Fire Alarm, 1965 (Box 35)
- [Handicapped Facilities Minimum Requirements], 1961-1980; (2 folders) (Box 35)
- HVAC Faculty Houses, 1973-1981 (Box 35)
- Handicapped Strobe, 1978 (Box 35)
- Handicapped Elevator. Lifts Field Notes, 1978-1984 (Box 35)
- [H. V. A. C. – Macon Valves], 1981 (Box 35)
- HVAC – Fuel Usage and Cost, 1973-1981 (Box 35)
- Lettering – Simple Space-Rite, 1986-1987 (Box 35)
- Library “Great Window”, 1973-1976 (Box 35)
- Library – List Of Old Plans In ‘Special Collections’, 1969 (Box 35)
- Library – Rekeying, 1980 (Box 35)
- NYS Facilities Inventory, 1971-1985; (16 folders) (Box 35)
- CICU and Regents Progress Report Information, 1978 (Box 35)
- Facilities Inventory and Classification Manual, 1973 (Box 35)
- N. Y. S. Facilities Planning “Space Utilization” [Correspondence and Summaries and Worksheets], 1970 (Box 35)
- Facilities Inventory Survey Correspondence and Summary Sheets, 1968-1971 (Box 35)
- Facilities Inventory Summaries, 1968-1971, 1976-1979; (3 folders) (Box 36)
- Higher Education Data System Inventory Report, 1977 (Box 36)
- Easements – General, 1928-1962 (Box 36)
- Deeds (Copies From Comptroller’s Office) (Box 36)
- Central Hudson –Easements, 1959-1968 (Box 36)
- I. B. M. Road – Smithfield Gore, 1965-1970 (Box 36)
- Sale Of Land Cedar Avenue To Central Hudson For Gas Regulator Station, 1969 (Box 36)
- Poughkeepsie – (Wing Farm) Pleasant Valley Route 44-55 Connector (Lot #4 – Jewell), 1967-1969 (Box 36)
- Easements – Richmond Hills, 1959-1960 (Box 36)
- Sewers, 1984 (Box 36)
- Sunset Lake and Casperkill, 1968-1986 (Box 36)
- Skinner Hall Acoustics, 1980-1981 (Box 36)
- [Specs – Various Frm (Brown)], 1988 (Box 36)
- [Taylor Hall], 1953-1978 (Box 36)
- Taylor Art Gallery, 1989 (Box 36)
- [Taylor Hall Addition – P. Rose], 1987-1988 (Box 36)
- Taylor Hall Alarm System [Security], 1971-1979, 1983 (Box 36)
- Tennis Courts, 1970-1987 (Box 36)
- N. Y. Telephone, 1957-1966 (Box 36)
- Van Ingen, 1962 (Box 36)
- Walker FH – Chemturf FL, 1988 (Box 36)
- Water Faculty Houses –Vassar L. Dr. Watson, 1959-1961; (2 folders) (Box 36)
- Murphy House, 1968 (Box 36)
- Electric #1, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
- Bio – Lab Job Meetings Only, 1972-1974 (Box 36)
- Colors - Bio Lab, 1973 (Box 36)
- Testing – Fairway, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
- Bio – Lab H. U. J., 1972-1973 (Box 36)
- Hardware, 1973 (Box 36)
- 3 - 3B - Site Utilities, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
- Architectural Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 36)
- Transmittal – Letters Of Reports – Drawings. Etc. [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 36)
- Misc. Items Sketches etc. [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 36)
- Sketches – Architectural [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- Primiano Correspondence [Biological Sciences Building], 1971-1972 (Box 37)
- 3 – 3B – Piles Foundations [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 3 – 3A – Cast In Place Concrete [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 3 – 3C – Precast Concrete Plank [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 4 – 4A – Masonry [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 5 – 5A – Misc. Metals [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 5 – 5C – Access Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
- 6 – 6A – Carpentry [Biological Sciences Building, 1973 (Box 37)
- 6 – 6B – Dry Wall [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 6 - 6C – Insulation [Roof, Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 7 – 7A – Roofing and Flashing [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 7 – 7D – Caulking [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 8 – 8A – Hollow Metal Work [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 8 – 8B – Aluminum Windows Window Wall [Biological Sciences Building], 1971-1972 (Box 37)
- 8 – 8D – Glass – Glazing [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
- 8 – 8E – Wood Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
- 8 – 8F – Revolving Dark Room Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 9 – 9B – Interior Tile [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 9 – 9 F – Painting [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 10 – 10A – Misc. – Fire Extinguisher’s Etc. [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 10 – 10B – Metal Toilet Partitions [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 10 - 10C – Shower Doors [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 10 – 10D – Chalkboards – Tackboards [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 12 – 12A – Carpet [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 13 – 13A – Skylights [Biological Sciences Building], 1973 (Box 37)
- 13 – 13B – Greenhouse [Biological Sciences Building], 1972 (Box 37)
- 14 – 14A – Elevators [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- 15 – 15C – Site Utilities [Biological Sciences Building], 1971 (Box 37)
- 16 – 16AA – Fire Detection [Biological Sciences Building] (Box 37)
- Biological Sciences Building Requisition, 1971-1973 (Box 37)
- Misc. Items Biology Lab, 1974 (Box 37)
- Biology Lab Paving and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 37)
- Biology Lab. Hardware Schedules, 1971-1972 (Box 37)
- Biology Lab Change Orders, 1971-1973 (Box 37)
- 11 – 11B – Library Equipment, 1972 (Box 37)
- 11 – 11A – Laboratory Equipment, 1973 (Box 37)
- [Addendum No. 1 To The Contract Documents For The Construction Of The Biological Sciences Building], 1971 (Box 37)
- [Dutchess Quarry and Supply Receipts, Biological Sciences Building] (Box 37)
- [Biological Sciences Building Plans], 1972 (Box 37)
- [Automatic Control System Plans], 1972 (Box 37)
- [College Dining Hall Fire Safety and Steam Tunnel Plans], 1972 (Box 37)
- Dining Hall [Outdoor Utilities and Sanitation], 1973 (Box 37)
- 15 – 15AA – Sprinkler [Biological Sciences Building], 1972-1973 (Box 37)
- Architectural Correspondence [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 37)
- Preliminary Architectural Sketches [College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 38)
- Dining Hall – Misc. [Electrical, Plumbing and Mechanical Correspondence], 1973 (Box 38)
- Glass – Glazing [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- H. U. D. Dining Hall [Housing and Urban Development Building Inspection], 1971,1973 (Box 38)
- Electrical Distribution System [College Dining Hall], 1972; (2 folders) (Box 38)
- Approvals – Drawings Etc.[College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- General Notes [College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 38)
- Saddles – Gratings –Manholes [College Dining Hall folded plans], 1971 (Box 38)
- [College Dining Hall Roofing Repairs and Carpentry], 1972 (Box 38)
- Benderson – Test Lab [College Dining Hall Fireproofing and Concrete Testing], 1972 (Box 38)
- Concrete [Receipts and quantity forms for College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 38)
- Rolling Fire Doors and Wire Grills – North American Etc. [College Dining Hall Folded Plans], 1972 (Box 38)
- Electric – O’Connor [College Dining Hall Folded Plans], 1972 (Box 38)
- Food Services – Misc [College Dining Hall Folded Plans and Correspondence], 1972-1973 (Box 38)
- Equipment By Vassar College, 1972 (Box 38)
- Fireproofing Plastering, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- Grease / Intercenter, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- Hardware, 1971 (Box 38)
- Hollow Metal Doors – Bictrite – Etc Hollow Metal Door Frames – Bictrite – Etc, 1972 (Box 38)
- Insurance – Damage Claims Dining Hall, 1971 (Box 38)
- Landscape, 1971-1973 (Box 38)
- Letters Of Transmittal, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- N. Y. S. Safety Insurance Reports, 1972; (2 folders) (Box 38)
- Painting, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
- HVAC – Steam Etc, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- Procast Cone Master, 1971 (Box 38)
- Piles – Wood – Steer, 1971 (Box 38)
- Piling – Frank, 1971 (Box 38)
- Rheinstein Const. Co., 1972 (Box 38)
- Roof Screens, 1972 (Box 38)
- Dining Hall Requisitions, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
- Roofing E. O. Osman, 1972 (Box 38)
- Specialties – Fire Ext Etc., 1971 (Box 38)
- Sprinkler – Mid Hudson, 1972 (Box 38)
- Job Contractors Approval, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- Skylights – E. O.. Osman, 1971 (Box 38)
- Toilet Fixtures Etc. Lockers, 1972 (Box 38)
- Plumbing – Fox, 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- Tile – Marble Etc Vinyl, 1972 (Box 38)
- Telephone Chargers, 1972 (Box 38)
- Wood Finish Trim, 1972 (Box 38)
- Sketches – Revisions, 1971 (Box 38)
- Details – Structural, 1971 (Box 38)
- HVAC – Ducts Etc.[College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 38)
- Misc – Ornamental Iron, 1971 (Box 38)
- Punch Lists [College Dining Hall], 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- Spare Parts Receipts [College Dining Hall], 1973 (Box 39)
- Old Punch Lists [College Dining Hall], 1972-1973 (Box 39)
- Items By Vassar – Later Date, 1972 (Box 39)
- Misc Items – Final Sketches etc. Outside Of Contracts [College Dining Hall], 1973 (Box 39)
- Job Meetings – Misc. Items, 1967, 1971 (Box 39)
- Masonry Modern Max, 1971 (Box 39)
- Memos, 1972 (Box 39)
- Misc. Architectural Correspondence [College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 39)
- Mechanical – Temperature [Fans and temperature control contract and letters of transmittal for College Dining Hall], 1971 (Box 39)
- Misc. Correspondence [College Dining Hall], 1971-1972 (Box 39)
- Vassar Memos [College Dining Hall], 1973 (Box 39)
- Dining Hall – Arbitrations, 1971-1973 (Box 39)
- Misc. Notes F. J. O., 1971 (Box 39)
- Sedgwich – Elevators, 1971-1972 (Box 39)
- Current [College Dining Hall], 1971-1973 (Box 39)
- Architectural Correspondence [Vassar College Center], 1973-1975 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Addendum #1, 1973 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Approval Sub. Contract, 1973 (Box 39)
- Requisitions, 1973-1975 (Box 39)
- Misc. Items – Reports Etc., 1973 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Change Orders, 1973 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Job Meeting Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- Engineer – Field Sketches [Vassar College Center Lockers], 1975 (Box 39)
- Architectural Sketches [Transmittal Form - Vassar College Center], 1973 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Field Sketches – F. J. O., 1973 (Box 39)
- Demolition [Vassar College Center], 1973 (Box 39)
- Excavation etc. [Vassar College Center], 1973 (Box 39)
- Division 3 – Concrete [Vassar College Center], 1973 (Box 39)
- [Fireproofing Products, Vassar College Center], 1974 (Box 39)
- Concrete Testing, 1974 (Box 39)
- T and M – Etc Extras [Labor and Equipment Costs, Vassar College Center], 1973-1975 (Box 39)
- Precast Concrete, 1974 (Box 39)
- Brick, 1973 (Box 39)
- Structural, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- Metal Docking, 1973 (Box 39)
- Misc. Metal Architecture Orwan [Vassar College Center], 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center Plans, Approved 2nd October 1974] (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Carpentry – Finish, 1974; (2 folders) (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Damp Proofing, 1973 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Concrete Waterproofing, 1973 (Box 39)
- Moisture – Thermal Control [Vassar College Center], 1974 (Box 39)
- Doors – Windows – Glass, 1974 (Box 39)
- Finish Hardware [Vassar College Center], 1973-1975 (Box 39)
- Glass – Glazing [Vassar College Center], 1973 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Metal Doors and Frames, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Wood Doors, 1974 (Box 39)
- [Copy – Pacific Rolling door Co. – Drawing A – 1, Vassar College Center], 1974 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Finishes, 1974 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Tile Work, 1973-1974 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] - Acoustical Treatment, 1974 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] Painting, 1975 (Box 39)
- [Vassar College Center] Division 10 – Specialties, 1974 (Box 39)
- 10-15 - Metal Toilet Partitions, 1974 (Box 40)
- [College Center] - 10-50 – Lockers, 1973 (Box 40)
- 10-80 – Toilet Accessories, 1973 (Box 40)
- 11-90 – Kitchenette, 1973 (Box 40)
- Division II – Equipment, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
- [College Center] -11-40 – Food Services Equipment, 1974 (Box 40)
- [College Center] Div. 13 – Special Construction [Music Practice Rooms], 1974 (Box 40)
- [College Center] Div. 14 – Conveying Systems, 1974 (Box 40)
- [College Center]– Plumbing, 1973 (Box 40)
- [College Center] - Sprinklers, 1973-1975 (Box 40)
- [College Center] - Electrical, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box 40)
- [College Center] - Fire Alarm, 1973 (Box 40)
- [College Center HVAC], 1973-1974; (4 folders) (Box 40)
- Phone Pad, 1973 (Box 40)
- Helen D. Lockwood Library and Alteration to Thompson Library Vassar College Project Manual [Official Office Copy], 1974 (Box 40)
- Charts and Graphs [square footage of buildings and capacity], 1969 (Box 40)
- Regional College Representatives, 1970 (Box 40)
- Correspondence [Higher Facilities Planning], 1969-1970 (Box 40)
- Space Utilization Manual, 1970 (Box 40)
- Questions, 1969 (Box 40)
- Sewers and Drains – Laundry and Service Building to Creek, 1940 (Box 40)
- Electric – Proposed A.C. to Ely Avla from Swift, 1945 (Box 40)
- Electric – Proposed A.C. to Ely Avla From E/. Manhole East of Ely, 1945 (Box 40)
- Electric – A.C. to Room #22 Rockefeller Hall, 1946 (Box 40)
- Electric – Lower Farmhouse (Weibeke) for Electric Lighting, 1945 (Box 40)
- Electric – Electric Service to Cow Barns and Rombout Measurements taken February 13, 1929 (Box 40)
- Electric – F.A. and C.B. Cables (2) from Nursery School to Palmer House, 1945 (Box 40)
- Electric – Distributing Board in Main Building Basement (Looking North) (Box 40)
- Electric – Proposed Electric Manhole By-Pass around Manhole #9, 1944 (Box 40)
- Electric – Kenyon Hall [Cost Estimates] (Box 40)
- Electric – Electric By Pass Around Steam Manhole North West of Chapel [Bill for concrete duct, 3 sets of Joint Material and Labor], 1933 (Box 40)
- Electric – 1928 Electrical Construction Costs (Box 40)